export default  [
    { 
        id:"1",
        question:"Who was the first female IAS officer in India ?",
        answer:"Anna Rajam Malhotra"
    },
    { 
        id:"2",
        question:"Who was the first Indian to become a member of the British parliament ?",
        answer:"Dadabhai Naoroji"
    },
    { 
        id:"3",
        question:"Who is known as the Flying Sikh of India ?",
        answer:"Milkha Singh"
    },
    { 
        id:"4",
        question:"Who was the first Chief Minister of Himachal Pradesh ?",
        answer:"Yashwant Singh Parmar"
    },
   { 
        id:"5",
        question:"For which book Rabindranath Tagore won the Nobel prize in Literature ?",
        answer:"Gitanjali"
    },
   { 
        id:"6",
        question:"Who was the first Indian woman to be awarded the Nobel Prize ?",
        answer:"Mother Teresa"
    },
    { 
        id:"7",
        question:"Who was the first Miss World from India ?",
        answer:"Reita Faria"
    },
    {
        id:"8",
        question:"Who was the first woman governor of a state in independent India?",
        answer:"Sarojini Naidu"
    },
    {
        id:"9",
        question:"Who was the first education minister of independent India?",
        answer:"Abul Kalam Azad"
    },
    {
        id:"10",
        question:"Which crop was most affected by the Green Revolution?",
        answer:"Wheat"
    },
]